7eleven.com.my 2015-12-26

# 7-Eleven Malaysia | Always There For You

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains our policy on collecting, using and disclosing your Personal Information. The processing of your Personal Information is also subject to applicable laws. The Personal Information which you provide to us now or from time to time or have provided to us previously will be used and processed, and continued to be used and processed by us, in accordance with this Privacy Policy (as amended, varied or revised from time to time). We may amend, vary or revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we revise the Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on our website.

In this Privacy Policy, 

"7- Eleven Malaysia" means 7-Eleven Malaysia Holdings Berhad (Company No. 1058531-W). 

"Personal Information" means any information in our possession or control that relates directly or indirectly to you (or any other individual) to the extent that you (or such other individual) are identified or identifiable from that information or from other information in our possession. 

"Products and Services" means any products or services offered by 7-Eleven Malaysia Holdings Berhad. 

"We", "us" or "our" means 7-Eleven Malaysia Holdings Berhad. 

1\. Personal Information  
1.1 What we collect from you

Personal Information we collect about you, include but are not limited, to the following: 

Personal details such as name, identity card number, age, gender, nationality, date of birth, address, telephone number, email address and other details. 

Information in connection with Products and Services you have purchased from us or have registered with us for purchase, services, information, updates, inquiries, etc. 

Personal interests or preferences such as language, product or content interests, communicating and marketing preferences. 

Other information that are, have been or may be collected by us or which you provide to us, from time to time, in connection with any service, transaction, contest, survey, promotion, questionnaire, forms or communication with us. 

Your photo and other image, by way of video surveillance installed in some parts of our premises as part of our security infrastructure. 

When you visit our website, there is automatic collection of some information about your computer such as IP address, web browser software and other information about your visit. 

Certain information requested by us are mandatory which you must provide and agree to the processing of such mandatory information by us, failing which, we will not be able to provide you the relevant Products and Services or information and updates pertaining to the Products. 

1.2 How your Personal Information is collected

When you sign up to purchase the Products and Services or register your interest with us to purchase or to obtain information, services and updates on the Products and Services. 

When you visit our website or social networking sites. 

When you enter contests or respond to surveys, promotions or questionnaires. 

From third party sources such as credit reference agencies, fraud prevention agencies and publicly available sources of information. 

Pursuant to any transaction or inquiry or communication made with or to us. 

When you fill in prize claim forms. 

1.3 Purpose of collecting and processing your Personal Information

To communicate with you. 

To process your application, inquiry or request. 

To provide the Products and Services to you. 

For administrative purposes. 

To respond to your queries. 

To conduct research and statistical analysis. 

To help us monitor and improve our services. 

To comply with applicable laws, proceedings or inquiries from regulatory authorities, and enforcement agencies. 

Any other purposes permitted by applicable laws. 

To market and promote other products and services that are or may be offered by us or our partners from time to time. 

For direct marketing purposes. 

To provide you with information and updates on the Products and Services. 

1.4 Sensitive Personal Data

We do not collect Sensitive Personal Data from you unless required by applicable laws. If you do not want your Sensitive Personal Data collected by us, please do not submit it. 

"Sensitive Personal Data" means any personal data consisting of information as to physical or mental health or condition, political opinions, religious beliefs or other beliefs of a similar nature, the commission or alleged commission of an offence or any personal data prescribed under law as sensitive personal data. 

If you do choose to submit your Sensitive Personal Data to us, such data shall then be deemed to be and will be treated by us as Personal Information which will be subject to the terms and scope of this Privacy Policy including as to processing, usage and disclosure thereof. 

2\. Disclosure

To facilitate the purposes above and the provision of products and services to you, we may process, use and disclose your Personal Information to the following classes of third parties: 

Regulatory authorities and enforcement agencies. 

Any court of law or any relevant party in connection with any claim or legal proceedings. 

Our contractors, service providers, consultants, and advisors on a need-to-know basis. 

Any actual or potential assignee, transferee or acquirer of any of 7-Eleven Malaysia Holdings Berhad's businesses. 

3\. Transfer Of Personal Information Outside Malaysia

Your Personal Information may be transferred to a country outside Malaysia. You hereby consent to us transferring your Personal Information outside of Malaysia, including to the class of third parties set out above. 

4\. Access Or Update Your Personal Information

4.1 - You are responsible for providing accurate and complete information about yourself and any other person whose personal information you provide us (for e.g., your spouse, children, relatives or third parties), and as such, as and when such information becomes incorrect or outdated you should correct or update such information by contacting us or submitting fresh information. 

4.2 - You may, by writing to us at the address set out in Section 7 below:   
\- Request for a copy of the Personal Information we hold about you.  
\- Request to rectify or update your Personal Information.  
\- Please provide proof of your identity, address and sufficient information to enable us to identify you when submitting your request to us. 

4.3 On receipt of your written request, we may:  
\- Comply or refuse your request to access or rectify your Personal Information. If we refuse, we will notify you the reasons for such refusal.  
\- Charge a fee for processing your request for access or rectification. 

5\. Limit The Process Of Your Personal Information

If you:  
Do not wish to receive offers, promotions and marketing materials and information on other products and services from us or our partners. 

Would like us to cease processing your Personal Information for a specified purpose or in a specified manner. 

Please notify us in writing to the address set out in Section 6 below. In the absence of such written notification from you, we will deem it that you consent to the processing, usage and dissemination of your Personal Information in the manner, to the extent and within the scope of this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the processing of your Personal Information as above, we may not be able to provide you the Products and Services you requested. 

6\. How To Contact Us

Write in to us at: 

##### Marketing Department

Level 1, 7-Eleven Malaysia Holdings Berhad,  
Podium Block, Plaza Berjaya,  
No. 12, Jalan Imbi,  
55100, Kuala Lumpur  
Email: [marketing@7eleven.com.my](mailto:marketing@7eleven.com.my)  
Tel: (+603 ) 2142 1136  
Fax: (+603) 2142 1139  
NOTE: In the event of discrepancies or inconsistencies between the English language version and Bahasa Malaysia version of this Privacy Policy, the English language version shall prevail.
